<resources>
    <string name="app_name">YEF_App</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="text2">My vision for this NGO is inspired by my own journey. I belong to a remote village in Bihar. Life has been through many ups and downs. To support my family financially, I decided to work as a child laborer in the factories of Kirti Nagar, Delhi. Just to cater to my family’s expenses, I worked in many fields like the carpenter, data entry operator, office boy etc. I somehow managed with my studies. Life has been too harsh to me. My perseverance to my education finally paid off when I achieved an Engineering Degree in 2016 from NPTI (Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University, New Delhi) where I was awarded a scholarship to pursue my education further. I secured 9th rank in University Entrance Exam. Currently, I am an Engineer in a German MNC where I’m working with the cutting-edge technology of Power Generation globally. I’ve had the opportunity to travel to Germany and other countries because of my job. Despite constant traveling and my busy schedule at work, I have not forgotten my roots. I am committed to serving underprivileged children to help them pursue their education. I not only fund my total salary to the Foundation but also spend quality time with the Foundation team and community leaders to guide them in achieving the objectives our foundation stands for. I inspire the students connected with my initiative since they can relate to me and I truly believe that changing their lives in a better way is possible just like I made a change in my life. I believe that life is to be utilized either for serving our family or society as a whole. The best utilization of life is when we live our life to make someone else’s life better. I consider the society as my family and I am working persistently towards its upliftment.</string>
</resources>